■
{\clip(201,214,201,216)\t(0,600,2,\clip(110,214,292,216))\t(4200,4800,2,\clip(201,214,201,216))}■
{\clip(80,216,392,216)\t(600,1000,2,\clip(80,192,392,240))\t(4200,4600,2,\clip(80,216,392,216))}翻\h译
慢慢的无敌小粉丝\h\h\h\h锅锅奶奶\h\h\h\h白小问\h\h\h\h莉莉斯内普
{\clip(201,214,201,216)\t(0,600,2,\clip(110,214,292,216))\t(4200,4800,2,\clip(201,214,201,216))}■
{\clip(80,216,392,216)\t(600,1000,2,\clip(80,192,392,240))\t(4200,4600,2,\clip(80,216,392,216))}翻\h译
黑狐狸尾巴尖\h\h\h\hVioletCheng_\h\h\h\h夏棒棒
{\clip(201,214,201,216)\t(0,600,2,\clip(110,214,292,216))\t(4200,4800,2,\clip(201,214,201,216))}■
{\clip(110,216,292,216)\t(600,1000,2,\clip(110,192,292,240))\t(4200,4600,2,\clip(110,216,292,216))}校对\h&\h后期
扒虾爬子大师\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(62,224,336,224)\t(1000,1400,2,\clip(62,204,336,224))\t(7600,8000,\clip(62,224,336,224))}■
{\clip(62,224,336,224)\t(1000,1400,2,\clip(62,204,336,224))\t(7600,8000,\clip(62,224,336,224))}片头推广合作洽谈：请联系普罗米修斯邮箱 PLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
克洛伊  嘿
Chloe! Hey!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
会被别人看见的
Someone could have seen you!
你得好好的藏起来  否则
You've got to be a good hider otherwise
坏人会找到你的
the bad guys will find you.
抱歉  爸爸
Sorry, Dad.
我叫埃莉诺·里德  今年7岁
I'm Eleanor Reed. Age 7.
我住在门罗街726号
I live at 726 Monroe Street.
我的生日
My birthday...
是3月9日
Is March 9th
10日
10th.
3月10日
March 10th.
我可以搅拌吗
Can I stir?
可以  但是得接着练
Yeah, but keep practicing.
那是我妈妈  南希·里德
That's my Mom, Nancy Reed.
她生日是8月10日
Her birthday is August 10th.
她真的会爱我吗
Is she really going to love me?
不然我们为什么给她钱
That's why we're paying her.
那是我的姐姐哈珀
That's my sister Harper.
哈珀
Harper.
她的生日是6月13日
Her birthday's June 13th.
她打呼
She snores.
你怎么知道的
Where'd you get that?
我以为我们该说到小狗了
I thought we were going with puppies.
是真的  爸爸
It's true Dad.
她打呼
She snores.
干得漂亮  克洛伊
Good job, Chloe.
这还真是妹妹会说的话
That is something a sister would say.
拍档万岁
Partners?
Partners.
我要是没回来你怎么办
What's the plan if I don't come back?
我就去贮藏室里
I go to my closet.
然后呢
And then what?
如果我把食物吃光了  就过街去
If I run out of food I go across the street,
告诉史蒂文和南希我是埃莉诺·里德
tell Steve and Nancy that I'm Eleanor Reed
如果他们肯照顾我
and I give them the whole shebang
我就把所有东西都给他们
if they take care of me.
我们再来复习一下旧功课  好吗  A
Let's go over the old classics, shall we? A.
A代表苹果
A is for Apple.
苹果是一种可食用的红色水果  很美味
Apple is a red fruit that you eat and it is delicious.
那你见过绿色的吗
You ever seen a green one?
-见过  -很好
- Yes. - Okay, good.
B是什么
What's B?
B代表棒球
B is for baseball.
是一种两只队伍对抗的游戏  每队9人
A game played between two teams with 9 players
绕着一个菱形场地跑圈
who run in circles around a diamond-shaped field.
克洛伊  你最喜欢的运动是什么
Chloe what's your favourite sport?
我从不运动
I've never played a sport.
你死了
You're dead.
这不公平
That's not fair!
你从没问过我这个问题
You never asked me that before.
要是你不知道答案  编一个就好啦
If you don't know the answer to something you just make it up.
你可以说
You go...
我不知道
I don't know!
所有运动我都喜欢
I love all sports.
那是撒谎
That's lying.
没错
Yes.
你得撒谎才能让人觉得你是正常人
You need to lie to be normal.
你觉得这有多少钱
How much money do you think is right there?
这些都是百元大钞  所以大概有几千块
Well these are hundred dollar bills so like a couple thousand?
远不止
More than that.
不  其实我也不知道
No, I'm not sure myself.
好吧  我加10注
Okay I raise ten.
我们晚饭过后可以吃冰激凌吗
Can we have ice cream after dinner?
你知道的  我们没有任何冰激凌
You know we don't have any ice cream.
你什么时候出去
When are you going?
一时半会不行
Not for a while.
我去商店的次数太多了
I was hitting the store too much.
我等不及变成正常人了
I can't wait until I'm normal.
你要不要跟我的10注
Are you going to call my ten or not?
你在虚张声势
You're bluffing.
那你试试
Try me.
全压
All in.
我输了
I missed the river.
你赢了
You win.
你越来越能从容应对压力了
You're getting good under pressure.
保持冷静
Staying calm.
这很好
That's good.
妈妈的眼睛也流血吗
Did Mom's eyes bleed too?
我的眼睛有天也会流血吗
Are my eyes going to bleed someday?
但愿不会
I hope not.
但如果出现这种情况  你得告诉我好吗
But if they do you're going to let me know, right?
好
Right.
你就说  嘿爸爸  我的眼睛在流血
You're going to say, 'hey Dad my eyes are bleeding,
什么鬼
what the heck?'
好了  现在把你的百万大奖收着吧
Alright now collect your million dollar jackpot
好的
Alright
确保你把最里边的牙都刷到了
Make sure you get the ones in the back.
我刷了
I did!
上次我检查
Oh well, last time I checked...
你头发打了好多结呀
Oof, there are knots in your hair.
好了
Alright.
呼吸时间到了
Time for breathing.
来
Alright.
闭上你的眼睛  深呼吸
Close your eyes, nice deep breaths.
吸气
In.
呼气
Exhale.
吸气
In.
你不正常
You're not normal!
一点都不好笑
It's not funny.
一点都不好笑  克洛伊
It's not funny, Chloe.
你得练这个
You need to practice this.
你看起来好好笑
You looked funny.
你得练这个
You gotta practice this.
这很重要
It's important.
要是我不照做的话就得去山上吗
And if I don't I'll go to the mountain?
你说什么
What are you talking about?
没什么
Nothing.
我从没教过你山的事
I never taught you about the mountain
所以你肯定是跟别人聊天了
so you must have talked to someone.
你已经去过外面了吗
Did you go outside?
没有
No
你看过爸爸的垃圾邮件吗
Did you go through Daddy's junk mail?
你是从那知道山的吗
Is that where you learned about the mountain?
不是
No.
克洛伊  克洛伊  克洛伊
Chloe, Chloe, Chloe.
现在不是在玩游戏  知道吗
This is not a game right now okay?
你绝不能对我说谎
You can never lie to me.
我没有说谎
I'm not lying.
你一直对我很好  妈妈
You're never mean to me, Mommy.
走开鬼魂  走开鬼魂
Go away ghost. Go away ghost.
走开
Go away.
走开鬼魂
Go away ghost.
只是你的想象吧
You imagined it.
鬼魂不存在的
Ghosts aren't real.
留下陪我  我害怕
Stay with me. I'm scared.
好吧  但我不能又睡了
Okay but I can't fall asleep again.
我睡着的时候外面的时间总是过得很快
Too much time goes by outside when I'm asleep.
我只能在醒着的时候保护你
I can only protect you when I'm awake.
雪冰先生与公主
雪冰先生
Mr. Snowcone.
哈珀  给我带一只冰激凌
Harper. Bring me ice cream.
拜托
Please.
给我带一只冰激凌
Bring me ice cream.
拜托  拜托  拜托
Please, please, please, please, please.
给我带一只冰激凌  给我带一只冰激凌
Bring me ice cream. Bring me ice cream.
哈珀
Harper.
有人吗
Hello?
嗨
Hi.
我给你带了冰激凌
I brought you ice cream.
巧克力的吗
Is it chocolate?
对
Yes.
你在这干什么
What are you doing here? Huh?
我给克洛伊带了冰激凌
I brought Chloe some ice cream.
你怎知道她的名字  你怎知道她的名字
How do you know her name? How do you know her name?
哈珀
Harper?
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
你知道不能随便敲陌生人的门吧
You know better than to knock on strangers' doors.
我真的非常抱歉
I am sorry about that.
我不知道她为什么过来
I don't know why she came over here.
没事  没事
No, not at all. Not at all.
好了  再见
Alright. Bye-bye now.
那是你女儿吗
Is this your daughter?
我们要去忙了
Oh we should go.
要去忙了
Gotta go.
你好
Hi.
你好  我是南希
Hi I'm Nancy.
你真漂亮
You're beautiful.
我的天呐  她真是个小可爱
Oh my goodness she's a sweetheart.
她看起来真正常
And she looks so normal.
埃莉诺  进屋去
Eleanor, go back inside.
快点  埃莉诺  进屋去
Come on Eleanor, go back inside.
哈珀叫你克洛伊
Harper called you Chloe.
那是南希  对吗
Was that Nancy, for real?
她怎么知道你的真名的
How did she know your real name?
你出去过吗
Have you been going outside?
没有
No.
不爸爸  贮藏室里太可怕了
No, Dad! The closet is too scary!
你知道违反规则的惩罚
You know the punishment for breaking the rules.
关小黑屋
Time out.
我差点就拿到冰激凌了
I almost got ice cream.
你打开了门
You opened the door.
你差点害死我们
You almost got us killed.
我是冰淇凌车
I'm an ice cream truck
我给世界各地的孩子们冰激凌
and I give kids ice cream all around the world.
噢不
Oh no!
有个巨人
There's a giant!
是哈珀
There's Harper.
她喜欢巧克力冰激凌
She likes chocolate ice cream.
克洛伊  你在我房间干什么
What are you doing in my room, Chloe?
你不能那么叫我
Shh you can't call me that.
你该叫我埃莉诺
I'm supposed to be Eleanor.
你会在爸爸醒来之前跟我玩游戏吗
Will you play a game with me before Dad wakes up?
你好吵啊
You are so annoying.
你为什么总是要在半夜叫醒我呢
Why do you always wake me up in the middle of the night?
我们可以像正常人一样在公园里玩
We can play at the park like normal people.
你可以在外面跟其他孩子一起玩
You're allowed to play outside with other kids?
你不怕坏人要杀了你吗
Aren't you scared the bad guys will want to kill you?
不怕
No.
所有人都在外面玩
Everybody does it.
没关系的
It's fine.
你有妈妈  我却没有  这不公平
It's not fair that you have a Mom and I don't.
你可以假装是我妈妈吗
Will you pretend to be my Mom?
你为什么这么奇怪
Why are you so weird?
那太恶心了
That's gross.
来嘛
Come on.
不
No.
做我妈妈  做我妈妈  做我妈妈
Be my Mom. Be my Mom. Be my Mom.
行了  好吧  我做你妈妈
Okay fine. I'll be your Mom.
说你爱我
Say you love me.
我爱你
I love you.
妈妈
Mom.
我想去外面
I want to go outside.
我可以吗
Am I allowed?
当然  你可以去
Yes you can go outside.
谢谢妈妈
Thanks Mom.
那我们搂着睡觉吧
Now let's cuddle and sleep.
对不起  我不该冲你喊
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
妈妈说我能出去玩
Mom said I could go outside.
克洛伊
Chloe.
她说我可以去冰淇淋车那儿
She said I could go to the ice cream truck.
想知道冰淇淋车里有什么吗
Want to know what's in an ice cream truck?
什么
What?
冻僵的孩子尸体
Frozen kid bodies.
我不信
Not true.
他们杀了小孩  然后冷冻起来存着吃
They kill kids and then they freeze them to eat later.
那我也想去
I want to go anyway.
你还不够正常
You're not normal enough yet.
你出去会死的
You'll die if you go outside.
不公平
It's not fair.
哈珀能去公园  我却不能
Harper gets to go to the park and I don't.
如果我给你冰淇淋你能不提这个了吗
If I get you ice cream will you shut up about this?
好
Yes.
如果你永远也不打开那扇门
I'll get you a whole bucket
我给你买一整盒冰淇淋
if you never open that door ever again.
我保证
I promise.
今天就给我吗
Will you get it for me today?
好吧  反正我也需要新的补给了
Fine. I need new supplies anyway.
谢谢爸爸
Thank you Daddy!
藏起来
Hide!
他们可能跟踪我了
They might have followed me.
爸爸  你还好吗
Daddy are you okay?
我没事
It's okay.
大部分是他们的血
Most of this is their blood.
谁的血
Whose blood?
怎么回事
What happened?
别担心
Don't worry.
我会没事的
I'll be alright.
就是要更小心点了
Just gotta be more careful.
我不能离开家  就为了愚蠢的不必要的
I can't be leaving the house for stupid, non-essential-
你忘了带冰淇淋
You forgot the ice cream.
什么  你懂不懂我差点就死了
What? Don't you realize I almost just died?
我自己去杂货店
I'm going to the grocery myself.
克洛伊
Chloe.
如果我们出去你知道会发生什么吗
You see what happens when we go outside?
我什么时候能去跟南希一起住
When am I going to live with Nancy?
计划有变
Change of plan.
什么
What?
我们还得躲着
We have to stay hidden.
多久
Till when?
Till when?!
无人机袭击了西雅图的一所房屋
瞧瞧这是谁
Well lookie here!
我能为你做什么  小姑娘
What can I do for you, young woman?
我们安全吗
Are we safe?
安全
Safe?
什么安全
Safe from what?
有人想要杀我们
The people who want to kill us.
有我在  没人能杀你
Nobody's going to kill you if I'm around.
我能要个冰淇淋吗
Can I have ice cream?
当然
Sure!
什么味道的  克洛伊
But what flavour, Chloe?
巧克力的
Chocolate.
一百美金
Wow, a hundred bucks.
你用一百美金能买一大堆的冰淇淋
You can buy a shitload of ice cream for a hundred bucks.
一百美金很多吗
Is that a lot?
什么叫一百美金很多吗
What do you mean is it a lot?
你想要什么味道你就能买到
You could buy any flavour you wanted with that.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Yeah.
到车后面  进里面来
Come around back. Come inside.
尝尝你想试的所有味道
Taste any flavour you want.
我不能去
I'm not allowed.
来吧
Oh, come on.
你再也不用听你爸爸的话了
You never have to do what your Dad tells you again.
上来吧
Come on up.
上来看看
Take a look around.
里面有冻僵的孩子尸体吗
Are there frozen kid bodies in there?
这只是一辆冰淇淋车
It's an ice cream truck.
来吧  我要走了
Come on. I gotta go.
还有其他孩子也要吃冰激凌呢
There's other kids that have to have ice cream too, you know!
但我挺乐意能有你这样的女孩帮我呢
But I'd love to have a big girl like you helping me out.
你还能自己做冰淇淋
You could actually make some of the ice cream.
给你
Here.
看这儿
Lookie here.
你会去公园吗
Are you going to the park?
我正是要去那的
That's exactly where I'm going!
上来吧
So come on.
发现任何情况
拨打  911
他们看起来跟我们一样
那是个好人还是坏人
Is that a bad guy or a good guy?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
他跟我爸爸一样流血
He bleeds like my Dad.
不是  他们只是把他打扮成那样
Well no, they just put that on him.
就像化妆一样
That's like makeup.
因为他们想让所有人害怕
That's just because they want to scare the hell out of everybody.
你的眼睛没有那样流血过吗
You ever bleed from your eye like that?
没有
No.
你没有对我说谎吧
You're not lying to me, are you?
那真遗憾
That's too bad.
推下我
Push me!
克洛伊  你能做什么特别的事情吗
So Chloe, can you do anything special?
高点
Higher!
你害怕的时候呢
How about when you're scared?
发生过什么奇怪的事吗
Anything weird ever happen?
再
Even!
高点
Higher!
我想摸到天空
I want to touch the sky.
我想触摸外太空
I want to touch outside of the universe!
没问题  飞高点
Okay real high!
去外太空  走你
Okay out of the universe here you go!
也许你能飞
Maybe you can fly!
荡高点
Go higher!
等等  不要推了
Wait no! Stop pushing!
再高点
Higher!
停  太高了
Stop! That's too high!
现在  跳吧
Now jump!
我害怕
I'm scared!
跳
Jump!
住手
Stop!
跳吧
Jump!
放开我
Let me go!
勇敢点
Have some courage.
加油  克洛伊
Come on Chloe.
从秋千上跳出去
Jump out of the swing!
我害怕了
I'm scared!
加油  跳出去
Come on, jump out!
加油
Come on!
勇敢点
Show some courage!
我害怕
I'm scared.
什么叫你害怕了  没事的
What do you mean you're scared? It's okay.
懂吗  过来  没事的
Don't you under- Come here. It's okay.
怎么了
What's the matter?
疼吗
Does that hurt?
疼
Yes!
生气啦
Does it make you mad?
是的
Yes!
那你真生气的时候你怎么办呢
Now what happens when you really get mad?
我深呼吸  冷静一下
I take deep breaths to calm down.
你能做到别人做不到的事情吗
Is there anything that you can do that other people can't do?
我没见过别人
Well I've never met any other people.
你知道怎么回事吗
Well, you know what's happening?
你爸爸要把你变成一个胆小鬼
Your Dad is turning you into a pussy.
你不能那样做
You can't do that.
你要像你妈妈一样坚强
You gotta be strong like your Mom was.
你认识我妈妈吗
You knew my Mom?
大家都认识你妈妈
Everybody knew your Mom.
你妈妈很有名
Your Mom was famous.
什么是有名
What's famous?
就是说她也有特别的天赋  就像你一样
Famous means she had special gifts just like you.
而且除了爱她的人
And everybody who knew her was scared to death of her,
认识她的人都怕得要命
except the people who loved her.
然后她死了吗
And then she died?
你可能不知道  但有个很远的地方
You may not know this but in a land far away from here
那有一座邪恶黑暗的大山
there is big evil dark mountain.
我听说过那座山
I've heard of the mountain.
我和你妈妈一起去过那座山
Yeah, well your Mom and I went to that mountain
我们想要摧毁那里  我们正
together, and we tried to destroy it, and just as we...
你们在干什么
What's going on here?
你还好吗  小姑娘
Everything okay little girl?
挺好的  没什么事
It's okay bud.
事实上  我们正要走
Actually we're getting ready to leave.
走吧
Come on.
我想回家
I want to go home.
你认识这个男的吗
Do you know this man?
不认识
No.
她是我孙女
She's my granddaughter.
他是你爷爷吗
Is this your grandpa?
不是
No.
她经常开这种玩笑
She jokes like that all the time.
闭嘴别说话
Shut up for a sec.
让我看看你的眼睛
Let me see your eyes.
为什么
Why?
明知故问
You know why.
我的天啊
Oh my God.
那是谁
Who is that?
是个坏蛋
He's a bad man.
他会杀了我们
He's going to kill us.
我还没跟你说完呢
Hey I'm not done talking to you.
没事的 伙计
No, it's cool bud.
你知道是谁想杀了我们吗
You know the people that want to kill us?
就是他
That's him.
That's him!
-闭嘴  -不要
- Shut up! - No!
不要杀我们
Don't kill us!
我不会伤害你的  亲爱的
I'm not going to hurt you, sweetheart.
快过来
Just come here.
你不用拿枪指着我们
You don't need to point the gun at us!
我们正要走
We're leaving.
他杀了你妈妈
He killed your mother!
离她远点
Step away from the girl!
让他走开
Make him go away.
我让你闭嘴
I said shut up.
快把他弄走
Get rid of him!
快
Now!
走开
Go away!
让我看你的眼睛  老头
Let me see your eyes, old man.
你走开
Go away!
听我的  到我这来  孩子
Look I said come here now, kid!
快走开
Go away!
走开  滚  滚啊  滚啊啊啊啊
Go away! Go away! Go away! Go away!
你是个很特别的女孩
You are a very special girl
我们要一起做件很重要的事
and you and I are going to do big things together.
我们回家吧
Now let's go home.
来吧
Come on.
全员戒备
All officers on alert.
桃树公园发现非常儿童
Abnormal child reported at Peachtree Park.
已经通知ADF
ADF has been notified.
重复  全员戒备
Repeat. All officers on alert.
你干得不错
You did good.
非常不错
Very good.
那是谁
Who is that?
那是你妈妈  我的女儿
That's your Mommy. My daughter.
她看上去像个天使
She looks like an angel.
那是当然的
Yeah she sure does.
就像你一样
Just like you.
我梦想着能带她回来
I have a dream to get her back.
我要去把她带回来
I'm going to get her back.
但她已经死了
But she's dead.
有时候天使能重回人间
Well, sometimes angels can come back to Earth.
能把它给我吗
Can I have it?
不行
No.
这是我仅有的一张她的照片
It's the only picture I have of her
我想留着它
and I'd like to keep it
这样我就能每天看着她了
so I can look at her every day.
拜托  别这样看着我
Oh come on don't give me those eyes.
给  拿着吧
Here, take it back.
租给你了
It's a rental.
别让你的鼻涕以及任何鼻子里的鬼玩意
Just don't get boogers and all that crap out of your nose
沾在上面  好吗
and stuff on it, okay?
好的
Okay.
我什么时候还能再见到你
When am I going to see you again?
等时机成熟
When the time is right.
比如你爸爸睡着的时候
You see, your Dad has to be asleep.
我有个礼物要送你
So I have a present for you.
当你听到我车上的音乐声
When you hear the music from my truck,
把这个放在你爸的食物里  他就会出去
you put this in Dad's food and he'll go out.
就像魔法一样
Like magic?
太对了
That's exactly right.
就是这个意思
That's what it is.
就是魔法
It is magic.
拿着
Take it.
另外  你知道吗
And you know what else?
女士  你再也不用藏了
You, madam, are not going to have to hide much longer.
克洛伊
Chloe?
克洛伊  克洛伊
Chloe? Chloe!
克洛伊
Chloe!
你在这儿
There you are.
你听见我在叫你吗
Did you hear me calling you? Huh?
吓我一跳
You scared me.
我很抱歉没给你买冰淇淋
I'm sorry I didn't get you any ice cream.
明天我去给你买回来
I'll go out and I'll get you some tomorrow.
我才不在乎什么冰淇淋
I don't care about ice cream.
我能来涂色吗
Can I colour too?
不行
No.
不行吗
No？
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
什么
What?
你骗我说的那些坏人
You lied about the bad people.
他们并不会伤害我
They won't hurt me.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
我要去跟南希住
I'm going to go live with Nancy.
等等  克洛伊
Wait Chloe.
我想要妈妈
I want a Mom!
你有妈妈
You had a Mom.
你不能像她一样
You are not going to be like her.
因为违反了规则而送命
She died because she broke the rules.
她没有违反规则
She didn't break the rules.
她很特别
She was special.
我也很特别
And I'm special.
别再那么说了  好吗
Don't say that again, okay?
我很特别  我很特别
I'm special. I'm special!
我很特别
I'm special!
我很特别  我能感觉到
I'm special I can feel it!
你不特别
You're not special!
别再那么说了  好吗
Don't say that again okay?
我恨你
I hate you.
你不再是我爸爸了
You're not my Dad anymore.
宝贝  对不起
Baby I'm sorry.
我只是想保护你
I'm just trying to protect you.
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
我没骗你
I'm not lying to you.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
滚出我房间
Get out of my room!
出去
Get out!
出去  滚出我房间
Get out! Get out of my room!
我恨你
I hate you!
我想要妈妈
I wish I had a Mom.
你真美
You're so beautiful.
你好
Hello?
你是鬼吗
Ghost?
你是谁
Who are you?
克洛伊
Chloe.
Chloe?
不
No.
他们给了我什么
What are they giving me?
你真的是我妈妈
You're really my Mom?
克洛伊
Chloe.
克洛伊  克洛伊
Chloe. Chloe.
不
No.
你不是真的
You're not real.
你们这些恶心的混蛋
You sick assholes!
把这孩子带走  不然我撕烂她的喉咙
Get this kid out of here before I rip her throat out!
我要把你们都杀了
I'll kill you all!
爸爸
Dad?
纪念达拉斯遇袭十周年
是那个纯种未成年非常人的报道
And that's why you came to town today,
让你今天来到这个城镇
because of reports of a full-blooded minor.
是这样吗
Is that correct?
是的  有一条有趣的报道
Yes, there was an interesting report.
如你所知
As you know,
非常未成年人是我特别关注的领域
Abnormal minors are my particular area of interest.
独家专访
ADF专家  塞西莉亚·雷
我注意到你用的是"非常"这个词
I can't help but notice you use the term 'Abnormal'
而没有用"怪胎"这个普遍使用的词
as opposed to the more widely-used 'Freaks' -
那是一种政治立场吗
is that a political statement?
我认为对ADF来说  尝试与非常群体
I believe it's important for the ADF to try to normalize
保持良好关系是非常重要的
relations with the Abnormal community.
非常群体
Abnormal community?
按照定义来说
By definition,
任何不受管控的怪胎都是非法的
any Freaks who are running loose are illegal.
宣布一群人是非法的
Declaring a group of people illegal
并不能让他们消失
doesn't make them go away.
只会让他们转战地下
It makes them go underground.
他们被迫为了生存而自卫
They're forced to defend themselves to survive.
那么就你而言  特赦法给了怪胎们
Well to your point, the Amnesty Act gave Freaks
一个和平搬迁到马多克山的机会
an opportunity to peacefully relocate to Madoc Mountain.
所以那些继续藏在我们城市中的怪胎们
So, the ones who continue to hide in our cities,
就违反了法律  不是吗
they're breaking the law, are they not?
我坚信搬迁并终止能力是对的
I believe in relocation and termination.
非常人十分危险
Abnormals are dangerous
我们不能任他们自由生活
and we can't let them live free.
但我也相信他们并非生来性恶
But I don't believe they are born evil.
大家都知道  他们的能力
Everyone knows their abilities increase
一代比一代强
generation by generation.
他们的后代被定义为
Their children are defined
活着的大规模杀伤性武器
as living weapons of mass destruction.
在他们还是孩子的时候就把他们给消灭
Isn't culling them as children
难道不是最人道的做法吗
the most humane approach?
但我只是
But I just
上一次那些怪胎孩子失去管控
I mean the last time Freak children were loose,
Dallas惨遭灭城
we lost Dallas.
想象一下如果我们能把一个
Just imagine if we could raise
非常儿童抚养长大
an abnormal child ourselves.
教导他们如何向善
Teach him or her how to be good.
有了引导
With guidance,
那样的孩子将会成为我军强大的武器
a child like that would be a powerful tool in our arsenal.
我迫不及待地想和你生活在一起  哈珀
I can't wait to live with you Harper.
过正常的生活
And have a normal family.
我们就能成为真正的姐妹了
We're really going to be sisters.
你妈妈会疼爱我
Your Mom is going to love me.
哈珀
Harper?
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
这是我的房间
This is my room.
不  是我的房间
No it's my room.
谁让你进来的
Who the hell let you in here?
我要跟你一起生活
I'm going to live with you now.
这位到底是谁
Who in the world is this?
她是住在街对面的怪胎
She's a weirdo who lives across the street.
我不是怪胎
I'm not a weirdo.
我知道怎么做才正常
I know how to be normal.
你有个怪胎朋友吗
Are you friends with a Freak?
她不是我朋友
She's not my friend.
我不是怪胎
I'm not a freak.
她的头发乱成一团  因为她没有妈妈
She's just messed up in the head because she doesn't have a Mom.
她真是个怪胎
She's such a freak.
怪胎  怪胎
Freak! Freak!
怪胎
Freak!
我不是怪胎
I'm not a freak!
怪胎  怪胎
Freak! Freak!
我有妈妈
And I do have a Mom!
她是个很有名的鬼魂
And she's a ghost and she's famous
她住在我的贮藏室里
and she lives in my closet!
怪胎  怪胎  怪胎
Freak! Freak! Freak!
看
See!
妈妈别害怕  没事的
Mommy don't be scared. It's alright.
那些女孩不在这儿了
The girls aren't here anymore.
走开  你不是真实的
Go away. You're not real.
你不是真实的
You're not real.
没事的  妈妈
It's okay Mommy.
别害怕
Don't be scared.
我的天
Oh my God.
我想你
I missed you.
你还活着
You're alive.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
我没死  妈妈
I'm not dead Mommy.
是你死了
You are.
我走了多久了
How long have I been gone?
才几个月光景
It's only been a few months
那时你还是个小宝宝  而现在
and you were a baby and now you're...
你怎么长这么大了
how did you get so big?
克洛伊  你是怎么进来的
Chloe how did you get in here?
我打开了门
I opened the door.
克洛伊  你在哪儿
Chloe where are you?
在我的贮藏室里
In my closet.
你爸爸在吗
Is your Dad there?
他在哪儿
Where is he?
他在睡觉
He's sleeping.
他总是很累
He's always tired.
你为什么住在我的贮藏室里
Why do you live in my closet?
我没有  克洛伊
I don't, Chloe.
我想永远跟你在一起
I want to be with you all the time.
我不想让你和我待在这里
Oh I wouldn't want you to be here with me.
因为你已经死了
Because you're dead.
我准备好迎接新妈妈
I'm ready for my new mom.
但爸爸说我不能有新妈妈
But Dad says I can't have her.
你的新妈妈
Your new mom?
南希
Nancy.
她住在这条街的对面  她会做曲奇饼干
She lives across the street and she makes cookies.
你去告诉爸爸
You tell your Dad,
告诉爸爸得继续生活下去  好吗
you tell your Dad that he should move on, okay?
宝贝  我很抱歉
And baby I'm so sorry that
不能一直陪着你
I can't be there with you.
但我不会再回来了  好吗
But I'm not going to be coming back, okay?
你得有个新妈妈
And you should have a new mom.
你得有个新妈妈  好吗
You should have a new mom, okay?
我们很快就来找你  贱人
We're coming for you soon bitch!
你下来干什么
What are you doing down here?
我看见妈妈了
I saw Mom.
她住在我的贮藏室里
She lives in my closet.
现在是我独处的时间
This is my alone time.
她说我应该找个新妈妈
She said I should get a new mom.
她说你应该向前看
She said you should move on.
别编了
Stop making stuff up.
我要去和南希一起住
I'm going to live with Nancy.
我可以成为正常人
I can be normal.
别闹了 克洛伊
Stop! Chloe!
你怎么了
What's gotten into you?
我希望你会死
I wish you would die.
总有一天他们会杀了我
Someday they will kill me.
你只能靠自己  那时你会后悔说这些
You'll be on your own and you'll regret saying that.
对不起  爸爸
I'm sorry, Daddy.
我给你做了特别的果汁
I made you special juice.
谢谢
Thanks.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
拍档万岁
Partners?
这是什么
What's this?
你想要给我下毒吗
Are you trying to poison me?
克洛伊  克洛伊
Chloe! Chloe!
克洛伊
Chloe!
这他妈是什么
What the hell is this?
你他妈哪里弄到的
Where the hell did you get this?
我为你付出了那么多
After everything I've done for you?
不要再喊了
Stop yelling!
克洛伊  你怎么能这样对我
How could you do this to me, Chloe?
快睡觉  快睡觉
Go to sleep! Go to sleep!
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
我是唯一能保护你的人了  克洛伊
I'm the only person keeping you alive, Chloe!
快睡觉  快睡觉
Go to sleep! Go to sleep!
你为什么要这么做
Why'd you do this?!
克洛伊  你为什么要这么做
Chloe! Why did you do this?
快睡觉
Go to sleep!
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我的天哪
Oh my God.
好了  每当你感觉要哭的时候
Here. Whenever you feel you cry
必须把眼泪擦掉
you must wipe that tear away.
它是你致命的破绽
It's a dead giveaway.
好吗  那是什么
Okay? What's that?
用来找新妈妈的
To get my new mom.
你的新妈妈
Your new mom?
你在说什么  你的新妈妈
What are you talking about, your new mom?
南希·里德
Nancy Reed.
算了吧
Oh come on.
我有个更好的主意
I got a better idea than that.
什么主意
What?
亲生母亲
Real mom.
上车
Get in the truck.
快点
Now!
去死吧
怪胎们
越来越近了
It's getting close.
再过几分钟就到了
Should be here in a few minutes.
现在  表演时间到了
Now... showtime.
我不想待在这里
I don't want to be here.
进去的时候  什么都不要说
When we go inside you don't say anything.
为什么
Why?
只要你别张嘴就好
Just don't open your mouth.
你吓到我了
You're scaring me.
你爸爸给你讲过独角兽的故事吗
Did your Dad ever tell you the story of the unicorns?
好吧  在附近的森林里
Well, in a forest very nearby there was
有一个大大的独角兽家庭
a whole big family of unicorns.
有一天晚上  一群咆哮的狼来了
Then one night a pack of snarling wolves came
他们走进了森林里  抓住了独角兽妈妈
into the forest and grabbed the Mommy unicorn
把她带走了
and took her away.
独角兽爸爸就在那里  他有武器
And the Daddy unicorn who had a weapon right here
但他却没有使用
chose not to use it.
因为他想藏起来
He wanted to hide.
他想做一个热爱和平的独角兽
He wanted to be a peaceful unicorn.
第二天晚上  狼群又来了
Well, the next night the wolves came back
他们吃掉了独角兽爸爸
and they ate the Daddy unicorn.
然后呢
Then what happened?
独角兽宝宝吗
The baby?
她孤身一人
She's left alone.
茫然无助
Doesn't know what to do.
她知道自己应该藏起来
She knows that she's supposed to hide
因为这是爸爸的做法
because that's what the Dad did.
因此她觉得  如果我这么做了
And so she thought if I do that
我就能平静地住在森林里
then I can live peacefully in the forest.
但你知道发生了什么吗
But you know what happened?
再也没有别的独角兽了
There are no more fucking unicorns.
躲藏已经没用了
Hiding is out.
那是她
That's her.
在隔间里
In the booth.
打扰一下  探员雷
Excuse me, Agent Ray?
能不能和您聊聊
Uh, could I have a word with you for a minute?
抱歉我现在没有空  神父
Sorry I don't have time right now, Father.
我有件事想告诉你
I have something to tell you
我希望和您单独来谈
and I need to tell it to you, um, privately.
守着门
Watch the door.
可以吗
May we?
请吧
Please.
我是神父汤姆·芬尼根
My name is Father Tom Finnegan
你和我有着同一个梦想
and you and I share a common dream.
什么梦想
What dream is that?
这个小生灵需要你的保护
Well, this little soul here needs your protection.
而且我们需要你带我们去马多克山
And we need you to take us to Madoc Mountain.
七年前一个新生儿被放在我教堂的台阶上
Seven years ago a newborn was laid on the steps of my church
和一张祈祷她能安全的便条放在一起
with a note, a prayer, to keep her safe.
我当时就知道我也许有了一个非常孩子
I knew right then I might have an Abnormal.
你为什么那么想
Why do you think that?
因为那时正是
Well it was right at the beginning
搬迁暴乱的开始
of the relocation riots.
你记得的
You remember that.
他们围捕了所有能找到的怪胎
They were rounding up every Freak they could find.
我有过怀疑  但我独自抚养了她
I had suspicions but I raised her all by myself.
看着我
Look at me.
可以吗  神父
Do you mind, Father?
请便
Please.
你刚刚承认了一项联邦罪行
You just admitted to a federal crime.
我知道我做了什么  女士
I know what I did ma'am.
但我也知道  如果在主的圣光里抚养她
But I also know if I raised her in the light of the Lord
教会她爱  她也许就不会变成一个怪胎
and taught her to love that she might never be a Freak at all.
我不是怪胎
I'm not a freak.
我是正常人
I'm normal.
没事的  她不会伤害你的
Um, it's okay. She's not going to hurt you.
你不需要伪装自己
You don't need to pretend.
我没有伪装
I'm not pretending.
你叫什么名字  甜心
What's your name, sweetie?
我叫埃莉诺·里德
I'm Eleanor Reed.
我七岁半了  我喜欢棒球
I'm seven and a half and I like baseball.
我爸爸叫史蒂文·里德
My dad is Steven Reed.
他喜欢钓鱼但他不是很擅长
He likes fishing but he's not very good at it.
不用这样了  你不用这么做
You can give it up. You don't have to do it.
我刚刚和你说过了
I just told ya.
我不会每次都和你重复两三遍
I'm not gonna tell you two or three times every time.
她爸爸
Her Dad?
她没有双亲  是我独自抚养的她
She doesn't have any parents. I raised her by myself.
我有
I do so!
我的妈妈叫南希·里德
My mom is Nancy Reed.
她的生日是八月十号
Her birthday is August 10th.
闭嘴
Cut it out!
我要打个电话
I'm going to have to make a call.
在你打电话前  我有一个条件
But before you do, there is one condition.
你有一个条件
You have a condition.
原谅我  但我必须留在她的生命里
Forgive me, but I have to stay in her life.
来继续抚养她
So I can continue to nurture her.
因此你要带我们两个一起去马多克山
Therefore you gotta take both of us to Madoc Mountain.
我哪都不会跟她去
I'm not going anywhere with her.
我不是怪胎
I'm not a freak!
嘿  快回来
Hey! Come back here!
你吓到她了
You scared her.
不是你的错
Not your fault.
收到  马上来
Copy that. On our way.
不许再那么对我了
Don't ever do that to me again.
永远不要给我退缩
Never wimp out on me.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
你根本不知道我费了多少力气才弄到
You have no idea how hard it was for me to get
那个婊子的行程
that bitch's schedule!
我不是怪胎
I'm not a freak!
我是正常人
I'm normal!
哦  不  不  没事
Oh no, no, it's cool.
我什么都没有听见
I didn't hear anything.
也许你是个怪胎  也许你不是
Hey maybe you're a Freak, maybe you're not a Freak.
我不关心
I don't care.
不关我的事
That's not my business.
没事的  没事的  没事的  没事的
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
你在害怕什么
What are you afraid of?
没什么
Nothing.
我能借你的笔用一下吗
Um, could I borrow your pen?
可以  当然了
Yes, of course.
完全没问题
Absolutely.
不  不要啊
No! No!
他的眼睛在流血
His eye is bleeding!
-开枪  -停下
- Fire! - Stop!
打错人了
That's not the guy!
不要开枪
Hold your fire!
我们得消失了
We gotta disappear.
操他妈的
Goddamnit!
靠
Shit!
那个男人会没事吗
Is that man going to be okay?
不  他已经死了
No he's dead!
他们就是这样处理找到的特别能力者
That's what happens when they find a special person like us.
你死定了
You're dead!
就这样
Period.
他们总是跟我们洗脑说马多克山
You know they always fed us this crap about Madoc Mountain
会成为我们的新家
was gonna be a new home for us
成为一个我们能够独立生存的地方
and a place where we could be independent.
他妈的原来是个死亡陷阱
It's a goddamn death trap.
你们为什么想住在那里
Why did you want to live there?
我们不是想住在那里
We didn't want to live there.
我们只是想进去  唯一的办法就是
We had to get inside it and the only way to get inside was
假装我们想去那里
to pretend we wanted to go there.
我神志不清了才会让任何人  包括你
I'll be goddamned if I'm gonna let anybody including you
妨碍我救我女儿
get in the way of me saving my daughter.
但她已经死了
But she's dead.
我搞不明白
I don't understand.
你不需要明白
Well you don't really have to understand.
看在老天的份上  你才七岁  还有你
You're seven years old for Christ's sake and you,
你现在得允许我教你使用自己的能力
you have to allow me to teach you to use your powers now!
我不想学
I don't wanna!
我只想南希来照顾我
I'm giving Nancy the whole shebang to take care of me.
你不可以这么做
No you're not.
你不能给她那笔钱
You're not giving her that money.
我们现在回家  去我公寓
We're going home to my apartment.
送我回家
Take me home.
什么
What?
送我回家
Take me home!
take me home
滚出我的脑子
Get out of my goddamn head!
送我回去
Take me back.
快点
Now.
好吧  我带你回家
Alright I'll take you back.
我的天啊
Jesus Christ.
操他妈的
Goddamnit!
下车  克洛伊
Get out of the truck, Chloe!
待在这里
Stay there.
不用担心
Don't you worry.
我来应付
I'll take care of this.
爸爸
Daddy!
外公刺伤了一个男人
Grandpa stabbed a guy!
我们还遇到了一个真正的大坏蛋
And we also met a real bad guy!
-但她是个女生  -到屋子里去
- But she was a girl- Get in the house.
气色不错啊  亨利
Looking good, Henry.
你跟我来
You're coming with me.
克洛伊
Chloe!
不  爸爸
No, Daddy!
我不想回房子里
I don't want to go back to the house!
我到处找了你一个星期
I looked everywhere for a week.
我想去南希家
I want to go to Nancy's house!
我真是受不了你了
I can't handle you anymore.
不  爸爸  放我走
No Daddy let me go!
我该怎么做才能让你听
What do I have to do to make you listen?
放我走
Let me go!
放我下来
Let me down!
放我走
Let me go!
克洛伊
Chloe!
你也很特别吗  爸爸
You're special too Daddy?
我竭尽全力想要保护你
I tried so hard to protect you.
我在房子外制造了一个时间气泡
I created a time bubble around our house
来保证你的安全
to keep you safe.
只要我醒着它就能生效
It worked as long as I could stay awake.
自他们杀了妈妈  我们开始藏起来算钱
For the rest of the world it's only been a couple of months
对世界上其他地方来说才不过几个月
since they killed Mom and we started hiding.
但对房子里的我们来说
But for us inside the house
你已成长多年
you grew up years.
一切都变得太快了
Everything is changing so fast.
我希望我能永远地停止时间
I wish I could stop time permanently
但我不能让你永远呆在气泡里
but I can't keep you in the bubble forever.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
一切都还好吗
Is everything okay?
我必须这样做了  史蒂夫
This has to happen now Steve.
你知道吗  我们正在吃饭
you know we're actually right in the middle of dinner.
我带了点心
I brought dessert.
好吧
Okay.
行吧  没错
Okay, yes.
进来吧  进来吧
Come on in. Come on in.
亲爱的  我们有客人
Honey we have guests.
埃莉诺
Eleanor.
妈妈  她怎么在这里
Mom why is she here?
我是埃莉诺·里德
I'm Eleanor Reed.
今年七岁半  喜欢棒球
I'm seven and a half and I like baseball.
甜心  你饿了吗
Sweetie are you hungry?
来吧  坐下
Come on sit down.
我去给你拿点吃的
I'll get you some food.
好了
okay.
你们要来吗
Are you joining us too?
-不  -不
- No. - No.
你应该早点通知我们
You were supposed to give us more notice.
这才一个月
It's only been a month.
我们还没告诉哈珀
We haven't even told Harper yet.
过了今天你们就再也不会见到我了
After today you've never going to see me again.
每个月你们都会得到一笔钱
You'll get one of these every month
只要你们不给ADF打电话
as long as you don't call the ADF.
-拜托好好照顾她  -好的
- Please take good care of her. - Okay.
我叫埃莉诺
I'm Eleanor.
我的生日是3月9日
My birthday is March 9th
我住在门罗街726号
and I live at 726 Monroe Street.
那是我们家
That's where we live.
哈珀
Harper.
你觉得怎么样
How would you feel
让埃莉诺在我们这住一小段时间
if Eleanor stayed with us for a little while?
她吗
Her?
对
Yes!
不  不  她很奇怪
No! No, she's weird.
哈珀  甜心  你怎么能这么说
Harper, sweetie. Why are you being like this?
晚上我在房间里看见她
I see her in my room at night.
她让我做一些事情
She makes me do things.
-什么事情  -那不可能
- What kind of things? - That's impossible.
哈珀你说什么
What do you mean, Harper?
她今天才离开家
She's never left the house until today.
她毁了我的睡衣派对
She crashed my slumber party.
是吗
Okay?
她强迫我
She forces me to...
她只是个普通的孩子
She's just a regular kid!
她是个怪胎
She's a freak!
行吧
Okay.
好吧  你知道吗
Alright, you know what
她让我在晚上拥抱她  亲吻她
She makes me hug her and kiss her at night.
什么
What?
也许我们需要更多的时间来做决定
Maybe we need some more time to decide.
好吧  南希 只是
Okay Nancy, just
拜托
Please.
我只是觉得我们需要
I just think we need to
我们不能拒绝  南希
We can't afford to say no, Nancy.
不  我们可以  我们可以拒绝
Yes we can afford. Yes we can.
那可是我们的女儿
That is our daughter-
我知道他是个怪胎  但她不是
I knew he was a freak but not her.
亲爱的  亲爱的  亲爱的
Honey, honey, honey...
不  别和我说这个
No! Don't tell me to.
别这么说  我们能冷静一下吗
Don't say it. Can we calm down for one sec?
就冷静一下  拜托
Just calm down for one second, please!
埃莉诺  你没事吧  一切都很好吧
Eleanor, you're fine, right? Everything's alright.
你是我爸爸  史蒂文
You're my Dad, Steven.
你喜欢钓鱼  但不是很擅长
You like to fish but you're not very good at it.
告诉我你爱我
Tell me you love me.
当然
Sure.
爱你
Love you.
妈妈  你爱我吗
Do you love me Mom?
你知道吗  对不起
You know what, I'm - I'm sorry.
这有点突然
This is all a bit sudden.
我只是需要再多一点时间
I just need a little bit more time.
我想你们该走了  我们之后再讨论
I think it's time for you to go and we'll discuss this later.
我只是需要多一点时间
I just need a little bit more time.
不  我们的约定
No our deal-
告诉我你爱我
Tell me you love me.
我们的约定是  她基本上是正常的
Our deal was that she was basically normal.
不行
No!
我们达成约定了
We had a deal.
当你考虑的时候
When you think about it-
我们的约定是  她不是怪胎
Our deal was that she was not a freak!
告诉我你爱我
Tell me you love me.
我觉得你们俩都该走了  别让结果失控
I think you should both go so it doesn't get out of hand,
拜托了
just, please.
告诉我你爱我
Tell me you love me!
南希  我们能考虑一下吗
Nancy can we think about this for one second?
告诉我你爱我
Tell me you love me!
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你  甜心  我爱你
I love you sweetie. I love you.
你是我可爱的小女孩
You're my sweet little girl.
放开我
Let me go.
她控制了我的脑子
She got into my head.
出去
Get out!
-滚出去  -收下这些钱
- Get out of here! - Just keep the money!
出去  否则我就报警了
Get out or I'm calling 911!
滚出去
Get out of here!
-收下这些钱  -对不起
- Just keep the money. - I'm sorry.
没事了
It's okay.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
对不起  爸爸
Sorry Daddy
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
我不想你生气
I don't want you to get mad.
这是什么时候开始的
When did this start?
当你眼睛开始流血的时候你应该告诉我
You were supposed to tell me when your eyes started bleeding.
她做了什么
What did she do now?
闭嘴吧  艾伦
Shut up Alan!
闭嘴吧  艾伦  你什么意思
What do you mean, shut up Alan?
不要  拜托
No! Please!
我不再相信你会遵守规则和保证安全了
I can't trust you anymore to follow the rules and stay safe.
你不能这样对别人
You can't do that to people.
我保证我会听你的
I promise I'll listen to you.
我不会出去了
I won't go outside.
你知道多久了
How long have you known?
你到底想干什么
What the hell do you think you're gonna do?
把她永远关起来
Lock her up forever?
我在保护她不受你伤害
I'm keeping her safe from you.
看在老天的份上
Oh for Christ's sake.
呆在像这样的垃圾里
In a shitbag like this?
你并不像你说的那样一直是清醒的
You're not awake all the time like you say you are.
别再胡扯了
Don't start with your bullshit.
她就是他妈的我们一直在等的人
She happens to be exactly what we've been waiting for asshole!
没事的  没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
没事的
It's okay.
嘘
Shhh.
没事了
It's okay.
♪ 在天空中 ♪
♪ Up in the sky ♪
♪ 鸟儿歌唱 ♪
♪ birds sing a song ♪
♪ 在云层间 ♪
♪ between the clouds ♪
♪ 歌唱它们的爱 ♪
♪ they sing their love. ♪
你会一直和我在一起  对吧
You'll always be here with me, right?
当然  甜心
Of course, sweetheart.
即使在他们杀了我之后
Even after they kill me.
我会在这里
I'll be right here.
就在这里
Right here.
好吗
Okay?
但你已经死了
But you're already dead.
我还没有死  亲爱的
I'm not yet, honey.
还没有
Not yet.
别碰我
Don't fucking touch me!
不要
Don't!
看起来你惹上面的人生气了
Looks like you pissed off somebody upstairs
所以你要付出代价
so finally you are going to pay.
不
No!
克洛伊
Chloe!
救命啊
Help!
救救我  克洛伊
Help me Chloe!
我说了呆在贮藏室里
I said stay in the closet!
他们要把妈妈带走
They're taking Mom away!
你妈妈已经死了
Your mom's dead!
她还没死
She's not dead, yet!
放我出去  放我出去
Let me out! Let me out!
你必须遵守规则
You have to follow the rules!
我们得救妈妈
We have to save Mom!
请放我出去
Please let me out!
这都是为了你好
This is for your own good!
我是在保证你的安全
I'm trying to keep you safe!
放我出去
Let me out!
爸爸  求求你
Daddy please!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry!
放我出去  放我出去
Let me out! Let me out!
放我出去
Let me out!
如果你不让我出去  我就杀了你
If you don't let me out I'm going to kill you!
克洛伊
Chloe?
Chloe!
克洛伊  住手
Chloe! Stop!
克洛伊停下  停下  停下
Chloe stop, stop, stop!
不要  不要
No, no!
对不起  亲爱的
I'm sorry love.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我不应该那么做的
I shouldn't have done that.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
说点什么吧
Say something.
她醒了
She's coming back.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这是我的错
It's my fault.
我只是害怕
I was just scared.
我不该那样对你
I shouldn't have done that to you.
妈妈在哪
Where's Mom?
你在那里看到了什么
What did you see there?
别说了
Don't start.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
如果她能看到玛丽  我得知道
If she had a vision of Mary I gotta know it.
如果玛丽死了  她怎么能看到玛丽
How could she have a vision of Mary if Mary's dead?
艾伦
Alan?
她还没死
She's not dead yet.
她还在山上
She's in the mountain.
什么
What?
你看
Look.
我发现她还没死的时候  已经太晚了
When I found out that she wasn't dead, it was too late
因为你已经带着孩子离开了
because you'd already taken off with the kid.
我的天啊
Jesus Christ!
我还以为她已经死了
I thought she was dead.
你把她丢在了那里
You left her there!
不  我自己都差点没能出来
No! I barely got out myself!
而且你知道吗
And you know what-
他们会杀了她的  她需要帮助
They're going to kill her. She needs help.
爸爸
Dad!
我当然会怪你了
Of course I blame you!
你逼着我老婆去执行自杀任务
You forced my wife to go on a suicide mission!
她是我的女儿
She's my daughter!
你把她丢在了那里
You left her there.
你可能只在这里待了几个月  艾伦
It may have only been a few months for you, Alan,
但我他妈在这房子里住了七年
but I've been in this house for 7 fucking years!
那是你的事  你这该死的疯子
Well that's your problem! You're fucking nuts!
你别给我发疯
You can't go crazy on me.
我们得成为拍档
We need to be partners.
说不定能救她出来
Maybe we can get her out.
我已经试了一次又一次
I have tried again and again and again while you're in here
就在你翻来翻去  鼓捣投信口
digging around and taping up mail slots
不知道搞什么鬼的时候
or whatever the hell you're doing.
我可不想讨论你那些荒唐的主意
I'm not talking about one of your ridiculous ideas.
进去只有一种方法  就是他们让你进
The only way you're going to get in there is if they let you in.
他们让你进只有一种方法  就是带着她
And the only way they will let you in is with her.
你可别想让克洛伊这么做
Oh, Chloe is going to have nothing to do with this.
不  克洛伊就得这么做
No! Chloe is gonna do it!
爸爸
Dad!
你疯了吗
Are you insane?!
-我没疯  -外公
- I'm not insane! - Grandpa!
我说的是事实  你从来都不接受事实
I'm telling the truth! You've never accepted the truth.
进去只有一种方法  就是带着她
There's only one way in there and that's with her.
面对事实吧
Face it.
她带我们进去  我们就能救玛丽出来了
She gets us in! Which gets Mary out!
爸爸
Dad!
怎么了
What?
狼来了
A wolf is here.
我们什么时候能拿到报酬
And when we do we get the reward?
等我们确认了他们的状态后
When we verify their status.
会有人安排好你的事的
You'll be well taken care of.
好的  你会把他们带去马多克山吗
Okay, and you'll take them to Madoc Mountain?
我不能让他们回到这里
I can't have them coming back here.
他们会知道是我干的
They'll know it was me.
马多克不是用来安置非常儿童的
Madoc isn't set up to handle abnormal children.
风险太大
Too risky.
而且自从玛丽·路易斯几个月前试图
Besides since Mary Louis tried to blow the place up
炸掉那地方之后他们基本就把那里闲置了
a few months ago, they've kept it mostly empty.
只有不反抗  嫌犯们才能到达那里
And suspects only make it there if they don't resist.
他们通常都会反抗
And they usually resist.
很好
Good.
那个怪胎夜间会对我的女儿下手
That little freak does things to my daughter at night.
你凭自己再也藏不住这个小女孩了
You can't hide this little girl on your own anymore.
我得帮忙了
I gotta help.
到我那儿去吧
Come on to my place.
我都想好了
I got it all figured out.
不行
No.
那就出去把你的烂摊子收拾好
Well then go out there and take care of all of your shit!
我已经不杀人了
I don't kill anymore.
我觉得这是克服
Well I suggest that this might be the perfect time
你不敢杀人的好时机
to get over that phobia
如果这人下令攻击  我们就完了
because if this man orders a strike, we're done.
我们会灰飞烟灭
We're dust.
明白了吗
You got that?
你好
Hello?
长官  一切还好吧
Sir is everything okay?
没事吧
Hello?
不要
No!
克洛伊  不  不  不
Chloe! No! No! No!
不  不
No! No!
她是非常人
She's a bleeder!
停止反抗
Stop resisting!
开火
Open fire!
看看你都做了什么
Look what you've done.
我做了什么
What I've done?
克洛伊救了我们
Chloe saved us.
她救了我们
She saved us!
亲爱的  过来
Come here, honey.
出去
Get out!
不
No!
艾伦
Alan!
放开我
Let me go!
放开她
Let her go!
让我下去
Let me down!
你在哪  你这个隐身的混蛋
Where are you, you invisible asshole?
放开她
Let her go!
放开我
Let me go!
让我下去
Let me down!
放开我
Let me go!
克洛伊
Chloe!
如果再让我见到你  我就杀了你  混蛋
If I ever see you again I'll kill you, you piece of shit!
妈妈  妈妈  妈妈
Mommy. Mommy. Mommy.
妈妈
Mommy.
Mommy?
克洛伊
Chloe?
是你吗
Is that you?
妈妈
Mommy?
你在哪里
Where are you?
他们在追杀你吗  妈妈
Are they killing you now, Mommy?
玛丽
Mary.
亨利
Henry?
我好害怕
I'm so scared.
装置已启动
Device is armed.
立即准备开始程序
Ready to begin procedure immediately.
开始吧
Go ahead.
动手吧
Do it.
我当时不知道你还活着
I didn't - I didn't know you were alive.
否则我绝不会丢下你的
I never would have left.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不
No.
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
别那样
Don't do that.
向我保证你不会让他们碰克洛伊
Just promise me you won't let them touch Chloe.
向我保证你不会让他们得逞的
Promise me you won't let them get away with this!
老天
Oh my God.
克洛伊
Chloe.
我爱你  好吗
I love you, okay?
妈妈真的很爱你
Mommy loves you so much.
别忘了这一点
Don't forget that.
妈妈真的很爱你  明白吗
Mommy loves you so much, okay?
克洛伊
Chloe?
我爱你  明白吗
I love you, okay?
-妈妈真的很爱你  -你拿那个干什么
- Mommy loves you so much. - What are you doing with that?
操他妈的  你不能这么对她
Goddamn it you can't do this to her!
克洛伊
Chloe!
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help!
离她远点  离她远点
Get away from her! Get away from her!
我靠
Damn it!
不许这样
Don't do it!!!
不  不  不
No, no, no...
有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
不  不  不
No, no, no!
住手
Stop it!
不  不
No! No!
我也爱你  妈妈
I love you too, Mommy.
克洛伊
Chloe?
天哪
Oh my god.
靠
Shit!
Shit.
不  不  别动  就一小会儿
Now, no, no, you gotta hold still for a minute.
就是这样
Just like that.
不疼吧  对吧
Doesn't hurt, does it?
我们得走了
We need to leave.
就现在
Now.
你让所有人都定住了
You froze everyone.
我已经筋疲力尽了
I'm already too drained.
我不能坚持太久  好吗
I can't hold this for long, okay?
那就让它恢复正常
Then bring it back to normal.
那他们就能进来了
Then they'll get in!
她想从里面帮玛丽越狱出来
She wants to start a prison break from the inside.
但如果所有人都定住  她就没办法了
But she can't do it if everyone is frozen!
我们得从这儿出去
We need to get out of here.
我不想再藏起来了
I don't want to hide anymore.
克洛伊
Chloe.
听我说
Listen to me.
坏人就在外面
The bad people are outside.
如果外面的探员出了什么事
If anything happens to the agent out there,
我们就没法活着出去了
we are never getting out of here alive.
我可以救回妈妈
I can save Mom.
这是我们最后的机会了
It's our last chance.
跟外面的女士谈谈
Talk to the lady outside.
假装你是正常人就好了
Just pretend you're normal.
什么
What?
就像你教我的那样
Like you taught me.
我本来不想直说
I hate to be the one to break it to you
不过你看上去一团糟
but you really look like shit
谢了
Thanks.
给  双氧水
Here. Hydrogen peroxide.
它会把你的眼睛弄清澈
It'll clear your eyes.
你知道还有什么吗
You know something else?
我支持你
I got your back.
我这有一件蓝衬衫  很搭你的蓝眼睛
And I've got a blue shirt that matches your eyes.
我的眼睛是绿色的  艾伦
My eyes are green, Alan.
是吗
They are?
不过谢了
But thanks.
你好
Hi.
有事吗
Is everything okay?
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to bother you.
我是特别探员塞西莉亚·雷
I'm Special Agent Cecilia Ray.
ADF的
ADF.
ADF吗
ADF?
这附近有怪胎吗
There are freaks around?
我们已经控制住他们了
They're under our control.
我能问你几个问题吗
Can I ask you some questions?
我其实正准备出门
I was just leaving actually.
我在市中心有个预约
I have an appointment downtown.
这很重要
It's important.
我能进去吗
Can I come inside?
房子里有武器吗
Any weapons in the house?
没有
No.
据我所知没有
None that I know of.
流浪汉们进进出出的
Squatters have been in and out
所以我也不清楚他们想要干什么
so I don't know what they get up to.
摘下眼镜
Take your glasses off.
所以你不住在这
So you don't live here?
不
Oh, no.
我只是屋主
I'm just the owner.
当初我买下了这里和其他六个破烂地方
You know I bought it with six other condemned shitholes.
我进来后  拆毁了房子  又重建了
I get in there and I tear them down and I build them up.
如果你想买  告诉我就好
If you're in the market let me know.
今天早上我过来查看时
I found all this stuff here this morning
发现了这些东西
when I came to check it out.
看起来这里曾经住过一个孩子
Looks like there could have been a child here.
你不觉得他们是怪胎  是吗
You don't think they were Freaks do you?
可能是
Could be.
非常人会藏身于这类荒废的房屋内
Abnormals are known to hide in abandoned properties like this.
真是令人恶心的动物
Disgusting animals.
你有孩子吗
Are you a father?
是的
Yeah.
没错  我有
Yes I am.
男孩女孩
Boy or girl?
男孩
Boy.
假如你知道他会被杀害
If you knew he'd be killed on site
难道你不会尽全力去保他的平安吗
wouldn't you do anything you could to keep him safe?
我会
Yeah.
我觉得我会的
I guess I would.
我很乐意见见他
I'd love to meet him.
小恶魔在夏令营呢
Little devil's in summer camp.
克洛伊
Chloe.
我们现在怎么办  妈妈
What do we do now Mom?
我得出去
I need to get outside.
除非我出去  不然我没法自卫
I can't defend myself until I get outside.
你能帮忙吗
Can you help?
好的妈妈  但我们要保持安静
Yes Mommy but we have to be quiet
因为坏人也在这里
because the bad people are here too.
好的  克洛伊  听我说
Okay but Chloe, listen to me,
在这地下我没有足够空间使用我的能力
there's not enough room for me to use my powers underground here,
所以我们必须在惊动他们之前出去
so we have to get out before they sound the alarm
如果搞砸了  我就再没机会逃脱了
because if it goes off I will never be able to escape.
你明白吗
You understand?
明白
Yes.
那好  来吧
Okay, come on.
那
So uh...
街对面是怎么了
what happened across the street?
里德一家
The Reed family.
原来他们是非常人
Turns out they were Abnormals.
老天啊
Oh Jesus.
我的房价要跌了
There goes my sale price.
你知道  我从来没觉得这个街区
I never, you know, thought this neighbourhood
会有怪胎
would have Freaks in it.
这样我觉得都讲得通了
Makes sense though I guess.
怎么说
How so?
你知道  当我在街上查看时
Eh well you know, when I was checking out this street,
我看见过他们
I saw them.
他们很奇怪
They were strange, you know.
为些事情指责他们的邻居
Accusing their neighbours of stuff,
一直撒谎  房子周围偶尔会有成堆的钱
lying all the time, random piles of money around the house.
那你都没上报吗
And you didn't report them?
我没觉得他们是怪胎
I didn't think they were Freaks.
就觉得他们挺混蛋的
Just thought they were assholes
但我觉得  真的看不出来
but I guess you really can't tell.
他们看起来和我们一样  对吗
They look just like us, right?
不管怎样  我真的要去赴约了
Anyways I really need to get to this appointment so...
坐
Sit.
下
Down.
什么
What?
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你说什么
Excuse me?
根据官方记录  这栋房子六个月前
This house according to city records
就被取消赎回权了
was foreclosed six months ago.
现属西部信托银行所有
Western Trust Bank owns it.
是的  不  我其实是开发商
Yeah, no, I'm actually a developer;
我和银行合作的
I work with the bank.
亨利
Henry.
我刚才故意把银行名字报错
That's not the name of the bank that owns it.
我还能从你身上闻到双氧水的味道
And I can still smell the peroxide on your face.
亨利
Henry.
你是亨利·路易斯  对吗
You are Henry Louis right?
你妻子是玛丽  我很确定
Your wife is Mary and I'm pretty sure
你的女儿就在楼上
your daughter is upstairs.
听着
Look.
在我看来你现在有两个选择
It seems to me at this point you have two options.
第一
One.
你可以尝试杀了我  然后我同事
You can try to kill me at which point my colleagues
会朝这房子发射导弹  我们全都得死
will hellfire the house and we will all die.
我们头顶三千米就有一架收割者无人机
There's a Reaper 10,000 feet above us right now.
第二  我之所以孤身前来
Option two, and the reason I came in here alone,
就是想说服你  你能帮助埃莉诺
was to convince you that you can help Eleanor.
或是克洛伊
Or Chloe.
不管她名字是什么
Whatever her name is.
我在听
I'm listening.
你好  罗勃
Hey Rob.
你看比赛了吗
Did you see the game?
道奇队赢了  兄弟
Dodgers are in, man.
要打季后赛了
Playoffs this year.
棒球是我最喜欢的体育项目
Baseball is my favourite sport.
好吧
Yeah.
是的  我也是  罗勃
Yeah, me too, Rob.
我也为人父母
I'm a parent too.
我知道你是为克洛伊好
I know you want the best for Chloe.
如果你邻居说的她的事  有一半是真的
If half of what your neighbours say is true about her,
那她真的不同寻常
she's remarkable.
对我们来说非常有价值
And very valuable to us.
有价值
Valuable?
是作为武器有价值吧
Valuable as a weapon.
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
是作为象征
As a symbol.
她和我们一起会很安全
With us she'd be safe
再加上合适的训练
and with the right training
她甚至可以为这世界做些好事
she could even do some good in the world.
难道你不想这样吗
Wouldn't you want that?
那我什么时候才能再次见到她
Will I ever get to see her again?
我想跟你说实话  这样你才能信任我
I want to be honest with you so that you know you can trust me.
你会被杀掉
You will be killed.
你会为了她牺牲自己的生命
You will sacrifice your life for hers.
我是说  你不是一直都在这么做吗
But I mean, you've already been doing that, haven't you?
我从没想过这个世界会把她变成一个怪胎
I never wanted the world to turn her into a Freak.
她只是个小姑娘
She's just a girl.
我完全明白你的意思
I know exactly what you mean.
那你呢
And you?
难道不把枪放下来  为了你孙女
Won't you put the gun down and do what's best
做该做的事
for your granddaughter?
地狱火导弹从发射到击中要60秒
A hellfire missile takes 60 seconds from launch to strike.
他和我都知道  这60秒内
And he and I both know that in that 60 seconds
我们会造成多大的破坏
we can do a goddamn bunch of damage.
艾伦
Alan.
冷静
Calm down.
我们还需要更多的时间考虑
We need more time to think.
道尔比医生在手术后没有回话
Dr. Daulby didn't radio in after procedure.
你能去行刑室看他在不在吗
Can you go to the execution chamber and see if he's in there?
收到  这就去
Copy that. On my way.
妈妈
Mommy?
他们要发现了
They're gonna find out.
克洛伊
Chloe?
不
No!
克洛伊
Chloe!
靠
Oh shit!
谁都别动
Nobody move.
你不会开枪的
You're not gonna shoot me.
先别发射地狱火  我带着女孩出来
Hold the hellfire. I'm coming out with the girl.
不  克洛伊  不  不  克洛伊
No, Chloe! No! No! Chloe!
-不  来吧  -老天
- No! Come on! - Oh my God.
你在释放她的能力  真是白忙活
You're freeing her. Such a waste.
不
Oh, no.
克洛伊  不  不
Chloe. No, no.
别这样
Don't do this.
你怎么敢
Don't you dare!
你不想要正常的生活吗
Don't you want a normal life?
爷爷
Grandpa!
我没事
I'm fine.
去找你妈
Just go to your Mom.
走吧  把事办完
Let's go get it done.
探员雷
Agent Ray.
探员雷  回话
Agent Ray, come in!
探员雷  我们听到了枪声
Agent Ray. We heard gunfire.
探员雷  收到吗
Agent Ray, do you copy?
我试着拖延一会
Let's try to slow them down.
你的探员在我手上
I have your agent hostage.
离开这栋房子
Move away from the house.
你继续
Keep going.
好的先生
Okay sir.
我们冷静一点
Let's just try to calm down.
我只想和探员雷说话
I just want to talk to Agent Ray alright.
你最好离开我的房子
You better get away from my house
否则我就用怪胎能力把你们的脑子都融化
or I'm going to melt all your brains with my Freak powers!
好的  没问题  先生
Okay no problem sir.
我们往后撤  我们往后撤
We're moving back. We're moving back.
我只想确认我朋友还好吗
I just want to make sure my friend's okay.
爸爸
Dad!
我没法帮妈妈  她定住了
I can't help Mom when she's frozen!
等一下  宝贝
Just a second honey!
发射地狱火
Launch hellfire!
后撤  后撤
Stay back! Stay back!
我们走  我们走
Let's go! Let's go!
动起来  动起来
Move it! Move it! Move it!
克洛伊  你能听到吗
Chloe, can you hear me?
我需要你
I need you!
克洛伊 我需要你
Chloe! I need you!
克洛伊  醒醒  我得出去
Chloe, get up! I need to get outside!
克洛伊求你醒醒  你可以的
Chloe please get up, you can do this.
你可以的  克洛伊
You can do it Chloe.
克洛伊  能听到我吗
Chloe can you hear me?
开门
Open the door!
他们要杀我了
They're going to kill me!
我需要你
I need you!
你知道去哪找我吗  妈妈
You know where to find me mommy?
知道  我能感知到你
Yeah, I can feel you.
爸爸
Daddy?
Dad?
爸爸
Daddy?
醒醒
Wake up!
爸爸
Dad!
能听到我吗
Can you hear me?
嘿
Hey.
我真的为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
我真的很爱你
I love you so much!
我真的很抱歉
And I am so sorry.
你很特别
You are special.
拍档万岁
Partners?
Partners.
不
No!
求你回来
Please come back.
回来
Come back.
不
No.
回来
Come back.
求你回来
Please come back.
醒醒
Wake up.
醒醒  醒醒  醒过来
Wake up, wake up, wake up!
回来  回来  回来啊
Come back, come back, come back.
靠
Oh shit!
妈妈
Mom?
克洛伊
Chloe!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
听我说
Listen to me.
从今往后  我会保护你的  好吗
I will protect you from now on, okay?
我会找到新的地方藏起来
And we'll find a new place to hide.
不
No.
我不想再藏了
I don't want to hide anymore.
很抱歉宝贝  但我们必须这样
I'm sorry baby, but we have to.
我们必须如此
We have to.
我们想在哪里住都可以
We can live wherever we want.
如果有人打扰  我们知道怎么阻止他们
And if anyone bothers us, we know how to make them stop.
好的
Okay.
准备好了吗
You ready?
好了吗
Yeah?
抓牢
Hold on.
怪胎